Notre Dame: Alumni Association
Alumni Association
1868-
ALM
68 boxes
University of Notre Dame Archives Notre Dame, Indiana 46556
Legal Status
Private
Access to university records in any format (paper, digital, photographic, or audiovisual) is governed by state and federal laws, University of Notre Dame policy, and the University of Notre Dame Archives Access Guidelines and is subject to review under the supervision of the Head of the University Archives.
Scope and Content
Records of Notre Dame's Alumni Association, including many photographs, videos, and audio recordings.
University of Notre Dame.
- Alumni Association: Records - CLOSED., UALM
- Alumni Association: Audio-Visual Material, AALM
  - Bob Pelton, C.S.C. & Mike Busick - N.D. Alumni Assoc., AALM A1235
  - Alumni Association Board Meeting, Notre Dame, AALM A1235-236
  - Alumni Assoc. Campaign for Notre Dame - Fundraising, 1979; AALM A1237
  - Gibbons, Jim - Phone Calls to Alumni in Cleveland, 1979; AALM A1237
  - Armstrong, James - Funeral Mass - N.D. Alumni Assoc., AALM A1238
  - Hesburgh - Sermon at Funeral Mass - N.D. Alumni Assoc, AALM A1238
  - Christian Ethics - Reunion '81 Seminar, 6/81; AALM C2319
  - Alumni Reunion 1981 Seminars, 6/81; AALM C2319-324
  - Mid Career Changes & Placement - Reunion '81 Seminar, 6/81; AALM C2320
  - Your Questions No Holds - Reunion '81 Seminar, 6/81; AALM C2321
  - Challenges of The Later Years - Reunion '81 Seminar, 6/81; AALM C2322
  - Admissions & Student Financial Aid - Reunion '81, 6/81; AALM C2323
  - Two Career` Families - Reunion '81 Seminar, 6/81; AALM C2324
  - Reunion 1979 - Ann Landers, AALM C2577
  - Vincent F. McAloon - Log Chapel 150th Anniversary - News Center 16 Broadcast, 1992/1126; AALM 9537
  - Vincent F. McAloon - Interview with Taddeus Jones at the Generalate of the Congregation of Holy Cross in Rome for Broadcast on Vatican Radio - English2000/0627, AALM 9538
  - Interview by Bob Probst (Class of 58) with I. I. Probst (Class of 26) and Mary Probst, 2001/0522; AALM 9948
  - Vince McAloon Oral History [recorded between 31 August and 21 September 1999], AALM 19126-19129
  - Fr. Arthur Harvey Oral History [transfer from reel to reel tape?], no date; AALM 19130
  - I.I. Probst Video [Hi8 Video], 2001/0525; AALM 19131
  - University of Notre Dame Visitors Information Video [Master and Revision], 1996/0529; AALM 26759-26760
  - University of Notre Dame Visitors Information Video, 2001/0608; AALM 26761
  - Spirit of Du Lac - University of Notre Dame Visitors Information Video, 2005/0706; AALM 26762
  - Spirit of Du Lac - University of Notre Dame Visitors Information Video [Various Revisions, Auditorium Version, Final Version, large shell cases], 2005; AALM 26763-26768
  - Monk - Teacher, President, Priest [Alumni Version], 2005; AALM 31030
  - Various Notre Dame Clips, mostly available on other tapes like President Reagan at Notre Dame, This Is Notre Dame Clips, Congressional Medal of Honor for Fr. Hesburgh, etc., no date; AALM 31031
  - Notre Dame Alumni Reunion Video, 1997; AALM 31032
  - Notre Dame Alumni Reunion Banquet, 1998/0606; AALM 31033
  - Notre Dame Exemplars Reunion [2 copies], 2000; AALM 31034-31035
  - Notre Dame Alumni Reunion Banquet, 2003/0607; AALM 31036
  - Notre Dame Today with Alumni News, 1998/0306; AALM 31037
  - Florida Fling, 2000; AALM 31038
  - Lesea Notre Dame 2000-01 Fall / Winter Sports Overview, 2001/0429; AALM 31039
  - Lesea Notre Dame 2001 Spring Sports Overview, 2001/0430; AALM 31040
  - I.I. Probst Video, 2001/06; AALM 31041
  - Fr. Malloy Address at Alumni Reunion, 2002; AALM 31042
  - Notre Dame Class of 1942, The Greatest Generation, 60th Reunion, 2002; AALM 31043
  - Vet-Ville - University Village, Video of Photos shot by Fr. Ladewski from 1956-1966 [quality is not very good], AALM 31044
  - Big Idea: University of Notre Dame - Myth and Legend, no date; AALM 31045
  - I.I. Probst Video [most likely the same as AALM VH 9948 or AALM VH 31041], no date; AALM 33512
  - Jack Sacco - The Music that Inspired the Book "Where the Birds Never Sing" [2 copies], 2003; AALM 33513-33514
  - Emil T. Hofman - Armstrong Award Speech, 1982; AALM 33535
  - Honorary President's Advisory Board [6 tapes], 1985/0419; AALM 33536-33541
  - Reunion: Invocation - Fr. Tyson; Remarks - Chuck Lennon; Presentation of the Sorin Award - J. Crowley, 1985; AALM 33542
  - Reunion: 1960 Class Seminar - 1990 A View to the Future and Predictions from the Past, 1985; AALM 33543-33543a
  - Reunion: Two Career Marriage Seminar, 1985; AALM 33544
  - Alumni Association Dinner, South Dining Hall [2 copies], 1987/0508; AALM 33545-33546
  - Alumni Association Recommendation Committee, 1987/0508; AALM 33547-33548
  - CCE Dining Area [tape one only], 1987/0508; AALM 33549
  - Reunion: Silver Jubilee Class Luncheon, Rev. Edward Malloy, Speaker [2 copies], 1987; AALM 33550-33551
  - Reunion: Banquet, Joyce Center, ACC [2 copies], 1987/0606; AALM 33552-33553
  - Alumni Board Meeting, 1987/0919; AALM 33554-33555
  - Alumni Board Meeting, Morning Session, 1988/0130; AALM 33556-33557
  - Alumni Reunion Mass, Luncheon, and Dinner, 1989/0609; AALM 33558-33560
  - Reunion: Silver Jubilee Luncheon, Joyce Center, 1991/0608; AALM 33561
  - Reunion: Alumni Banquet, Joyce Center, 1991/0609; AALM 33562-33563
  - Reunion: Alumni Weekend Opening Lunch, 1993; AALM 33564
  - Reunion: Silver Jubilee Lunch, 1993/0605; AALM 33565
  - Reunion: Alumni Banquet, 1993; AALM 33566-33567
  - Reunion: Father Hesburgh Speech, 1985/0608; AALM 33568
  - Reunion Luncheon: Fr. Hesburgh Speech, Reunion Banquet: Fr. Hesburgh Speech [2 copies for Banquet Speech], 1986; AALM 33569-33571
  - Alumni Reunion: Fr. Hesburgh speech at Dinner [tape 1 only], 1987/0507; AALM 33572
  - Chuck Lennon Speech at Alumni Family Hall, 1982; AALM 33573
  - 2008 Notre Dame Reunion Films: APA, Law School, 2003, 1998, 1993, 1988, 1983, 1978, 1973, 1968, 1963, 1958, 50 Year Club, AALM 34843
  - Scholarship Info, developed by Frank Kelly [tape for slides], 1983; AALM 40727
  - The Irish Madonna, Blessing and Dedication Ceremonies [long box], 2007/0428; AALM 45672
  - Big Idea: James F. Armstrong Award for Rex Rakow [2 copies], 2007/05; AALM 45673-45674
  - Monk - Teacher, Priest, President [Diversity Version], 2005/0401; AALM 45675
  - Notre Dame Legends - Bud Dudley, Class of '43 [long box], 2000s; AALM 45676
  - Notre Dame Legends - Bob Kuehner, Class of '50 [long box], 2000s; AALM 45677
  - Knute Rockne Sculpture Unveiling, Voss Norway, Jerry McKenna - Sculptor [long box], 2006/0331; AALM 45678
  - Holy Cross in East Africa, Formation, Education, Parishes, social work, Health Care, history [Holy Cross Media Ministry, long box], 2005/03; AALM 45679
  - Corporate Time [cassette removed from AALM 2010-172, Alumni Publications Edition], no date; AALM 46035
  - Notre Dame Alumni Association, Southern California Communion Breakfast Video, Haiti footage, etc., 2000; AALM 46036-46037
  - Alumni Social Concerns Forum - Panel Discussion Saturday Night, 1995; AALM 46038
  - Spirit of Du Lac, Visitor's Center Version [Draft 5], 2005/0905; AALM 46039
  - STEP Institute Day, Lecture 8: Fr. Michael Baxter - The Church and the Contemporary World [with intro], 2002/0126; AALM 46040
  - Alumni Reunion, The Chuck and Joan Lennon Family Eucharistic Lecture Series - Rev. William D. Seetch, CSC, Alumni Chaplain, 2005; AALM 46041
  - Fields of Dreams, Cleveland Housing Film, ca. 1980s; AALM 46046
  - Notre Dame Alumni Association / Monogram Club: Nowhere But Notre Dame - University of Notre Dame Athletics Highlight Video [long box], 2005/2006; AALM 46065
  - Dan Towle - Six Degrees of Hope: The Plight of Lesotho, Africa, Touching Tiny Lives Organization [long box, removed from UALM 2010-172, 7/04], 2005; AALM 47118
  - Big Idea - Rex J. Rakow, Armstrong Award Acceptance [removed from UALM 2010-172 5/38], 2007/05; AALM 47119
  - Football: Notre Dame vs. Ohio State, Fiesta Bowl [Pre-Game Show], 2006; AALM 47961
  - Football: Notre Dame vs. Georgia Tech [Countdown to Kickoff], 2006; AALM 47962
  - Football: Notre Dame vs. Penn State [Countdown to Kickoff, Irish Sports Report, 2 copies], 2006/0909; AALM 47963-47964
  - Football: Notre Dame vs. Michigan [Countdown to Kickoff], 2006/0916; AALM 47965
  - Football: Notre Dame vs. MSU / Michigan State [Blue and Gold Irish Weekly], 2006; AALM 47966
  - Football: Notre Dame vs. Purdue [Countdown to Kickoff, Irish Sports Report], 2006; AALM 47967
  - Football: Notre Dame vs. Stanford [Countdown to Kickoff, Irish Sports Report], 2006; AALM 47968
  - Football: Notre Dame vs. UCLA [Countdown to Kickoff, Irish Sports Report], 2006; AALM 47969
  - Football: Notre Dame vs. Navy [Pregame, Irish Sports Report], 2006; AALM 47970
  - Football: Notre Dame vs. north Carolina [Pregame, Irish Sports Report], 2006; AALM 47971
  - Football: Notre Dame vs. USC [Pregame, Irish Weekly, Irish Sports Report], 2006; AALM 47972
  - Football: Notre Dame vs. Air Force [Irish Sports Report]; Notre Dame vs. Army [Countdown to Kickoff and Irish Sports Report], 2006; AALM 47973
  - Football: Notre Dame vs. LSU, Sugar Bowl [Irish Sports Report], 2007; AALM 47974
  - Football: Notre Dame vs. Nevada [Pregame Show], 2009; AALM 47975
  - Football: Notre Dame vs. Michigan State / MSU [Pregame Show], 2009; AALM 47976
  - Football: Notre Dame vs. Washington [Pregame Show], 2009; AALM 47977
  - Football: Notre Dame vs. USC [Pregame Show], 2009; AALM 47978
  - Football: Notre Dame vs. Boston College [Pregame Show, Post Game Show], 2009; AALM 47979
  - Football: Notre Dame vs. Washington State [Pregame Show], 2009; AALM 47980
  - Football: Notre Dame vs. Navy [Pregame Show, Postgame Show], 2009; AALM 47981
  - Football: Notre Dame vs. Connecticut [Pregame Show], 2009; AALM 47982
  - Nothing But Victory, The Notre Dame Victory March, Various Piano Versions, Joe Probst, 2004; AALM 47983
  - Notre Dame vs USC Football Luncheon, 2006; AALM 47984
  - The University of Notre Dame Concert Band- The Road to Carnegie Hall, directed by Ken Dye, 2010; AALM 47985
  - Spirit of du Lac [Big Idea Company, ca. 12 min.], 2005/0930; AALM 47986
  - Spirit of du Lac [Big Idea Company, ca. 30 min.], 2005/1028; AALM 47987
  - Spirit of du Lac [Big Idea Company, Draft 2 Master], 2005; AALM 47988
  - Spirit of du Lac [Big Idea Company, Academic / Auditorium Version], 2005; AALM 47989
  - Spirit of du Lac [Big Idea Company, Winter Sports Version, 3 copies], 2005; AALM 47990-47992
  - Notre Dame Alumni Reunion Banquet, 2007; AALM 47993
  - Notre Dame Alumni Reunion Videos, Fifty Year Club, First Women, Hispanic Alumni, Law School, 2002, 1997, 1992, 1987, 1982, 1977, 1972, 1967, 1962, 1957, Fr. Theodore Hesburgh, Andy Williams [2 copies], 2007; AALM 47994-47995
  - Notre Dame Public Affairs and Communications - Gene Bastedo and Dick Nussbaum Comments [Pentavision], 2006/0925; AALM 47996
  - Prayer Reflections at Notre Dame, no date; AALM 47997
  - The Art of Living: John Feight, Paint Fest at Notre Dame, 2006/1219; AALM 47998
  - Home for Christmas, A Benefit Recording for the YMCA Urban Youth Scholarship Fund with Lou Holtz and the Notre Dame Glee Club [Acorn Records], 1991; AALM 47999
  - Tim Stopulos - The Long Drive Home, 2007; AALM 48000
  - Daughters of Notre Dame - A Generation of Inspiration [Big Idea, long box], 2007; AALM 48001
  - The Irish Madonna, Blessing and Dedication Ceremonies [Big idea, long box, 3 copies], 2007/0428; AALM 48002-48004
  - NBC Nightly News with Tom Brokaw - Home of the Brave Segment with Mario Motts Tonelli, 1998/0217; AALM 48005
  - Regis Philbin on A&E Biography, 1998; AALM 48006
  - Notre Dame Football Highlights, Football Seniors Video, 2004; AALM 48007
  - University of Notre Dame Athletics Highlight Video, 2003/2004; AALM 48008
  - NBC Dateline, Hoop Dreams with Mike Edwards, 1998/0531; AALM 48009
  - Short Video Slideshow of Aubrey Lewis Photos and Video, 2001; AALM 48010
  - We Are The Black Alumni of Notre Dame, 2000; AALM 48011
  - The 20 Greatest Notre Dame Football Moments of the Past 100 Years [Host Sports], 1992; AALM 48012
  - Orientation for New Faculty Athletics Representatives, 1994; AALM 48013
  - Christmas music performed by the Notre Dame Glee Club [Golden Dome Productions, 2 copies], 1991; AALM 48014-48015
  - The Strength of Notre Dame. A Strength and Conditioning Program for the Student Athlete [Universal Gym Equipment, Inc.], 1988; AALM 48016
  - Buddy Farmer - Coaches, Off the Bench with Knute, Vince and the Bear [Viewing Copy], 1994/0302; AALM 48017
  - Wake Up the Echoes, Notre Dame's Greatest Victories, vol 2 - Bowl Victories, 1995; AALM 48018
  - Henri Nouwen's Passion and Spirituality [Golden Dome Productions / Center for Social Concerns], 2001; AALM 48019
  - Notre Dame Oral History Project Montage / Presentation, 2008; AALM 48025
  - Notre Dame's Chuck Lennon, Her Loyal Son, Retirement Function [2 copies], 2011/0415; AALM 48649-48650
  - Notre Dame's Chuck Lennon, Her Loyal Son, Pictures, Videos and Comments from Friends and Co-Workers [New Group Media, 2 copies], 2011; AALM 48651-48652
  - Harry Murphy, ND Class of 1959 Oral History about a moment he shared with his son at the Grotto done by Katie Freddoso [do not copy], 2007; AALM 48723
  - Dr. Paul Wright, ND Class of 1972 Oral History about what he learned from Mother Teresa about working with the sick done by Katie Freddoso [do not copy], 2007; AALM 48723
  - Cavanaugh and Rosenthal Award Recipients, Terrence E. Sauvain Sr.; Paul Bonitatibus; Michael O. Read; and Rod West., 2006/0928; AALM 48724
  - Chuck Lennon, 25 years [2 copies], 2007/0125; AALM 48725-48726
  - Notre Dame Alumni Reunion Videos, Fifty Year Club, First Women, Hispanic Alumni, Law School, 2002, 1997, 1992, 1987, 1982, 1977, 1972, 1967, 1962, 1957, Fr. Thedore Hesburgh, Andy Williams [draft #3], 2007; AALM 48727
  - Kathleen Sullivan, The O'Neill Brothers: Prayer, Always In Season, Vol. 1 [Wake Up, Food For The Journey][removed from UALM 2013-61, 1/28], 2009; AALM 51848
  - Kathleen Sullivan, The O'Neill Brothers: Prayer, Always In Season [Wake Up, Food For The Journey][removed from UALM 2013-61, 1/28], 2008; AALM 51849
  - Joseph Campbell; Tom Morris; Coleman Barks; Tian Dayton; Eileen Egan; Alexander Constantine: Inspiration, Wellness, Prayer [Wake Up, Food For The Journey][2 copies][removed from UALM 2013-61, 1/28], 2007; AALM 51850-51851
  - Notre Dame Commencement Addresses, 2009/0517; AALM 52267
  - Holy Family Surgery Center, Providing Surgical Solutions in Honduras [removed from UALM # 2013-259, 3/4], no date; AALM 52863
  - Festival of Trees, Health East Foundation, Daly Tribute: Angels of Mercy [removed from UALM # 2013-259, 3/4], 2010; AALM 52864
  - This Is Notre Dame - Audiovisual Presentation [Slide show with audio cassette], 1978; AALM 52884
  - NDAA on the Sidelines / Football Friday Academic Series Presentation of "Her Loyal Sons and Daughters: Exploring the Rich History of the Notre Dame Black Student Experience, featuring David Krashna and Don Wycliff.", 2014/0820; AALM 55212
  - Notre Dame Alumni Reunion - Fr. Theodore Hesburgh Remarks at Black Alumni Dinner and His First Visit with Barack Obama, 2009/0605; AALM 58704
  - Mass from the Basilica of the Sacred Heart, Rev. Daniel Ponisciak, CSC, 2015/0412; AALM 66392
  - Tender, Strong, And True - Job Loss, 2011; AALM 66393
  - Tender, Strong, And True #3 - Living The Gospel [quicktime files], 2010; AALM 66394
  - Notre Dame Prayer Teleconference, Part 1 [Clips from Web, quicktime files], 2010; AALM 66395
  - Pray At Notre Dame - Sacred Spaces [Holy Cross Media Ministry], 2010/0810; AALM 66396
  - Pray.ND.EDU - Perservering in Prayer, 2010; AALM 66397
  - Insights from Fr. John Dunne, CSC, Alumni Association Retreat Toolkit, 2012; AALM 66398
  - Tender, Strong, And True #3 - Living The Gospel [Discovering Your Mission: Living With God Given Purpose], 2010; AALM 66399
  - John Dunn ['58] - Danny Boy, Tribute Sung to Theodore Hesburgh, no date; AALM 69172
  - Spirit of Du Lac - Spring Sports Version, 2005; AALM 79770; Swimming, Football, Track and Field, Golf [Draft 2] [disc is damaged but data has been retrieved] [Big Idea Company]
  - Notre Dame Film, Television, and Theatre - Making Movies, Films, c2002; AALM 79771; The School; Lungwamen; Moment; Time and Temperature; Polaroid; Checkout
  - Notre Dame Film, Television, and Theatre - Student Films, c2003; AALM 79772; Cable Ready; Untitled #3; Is Your Money That Cool?; College U; Pop Loser; Burt's Riff; The School; Thump; Lungwamen; Comic Book Life; PSAs 1998; The Hat; 3 Seconds Into the Future; Success; Daniel P. Sternan; Une Vrai Romance; Moment; Ramona's Roses; Radio Play; Minimum Wage Wrangler; Big White Box; National PAstime; Late One Night; Search, Pause; Play, Reload; Rollerskating Romance; The Dying Soldier; Blind Date #42; Josephine; Polaroid; Two in the Smoker; PSAs 2001; The Paper; Time and Temperature; Fern; Checkout; Adam's Puzzle
  - University of Notre Dame: Self-Guided Audio CD Tour, An Interactive Tour of Campus Landmarks [CD-rom], no date; AALM 79773
  - Make God Known, Loved and Served, Basil Anthony Moreau, CSC, no date; AALM 79774
  - University of Notre Dame Visitors Information video [2 copies], 1999; AALM 79775-79776
  - Spirit of Du Lac - Fall Sports Version: Tennis, Soccer [Draft 2][Big Idea Company], 2005; AALM 79777
  - Spirit of Du Lac - Fall Sport Version [3 copies][Big Idea Company], 2005; AALM 79778-79780
  - College Football Hall of Fame Visitors Video [Pathfinders], 2003/0820; AALM 79781
  - Generations: Stories of Notre Dame, includes Notre Dame Archives and Charles Lamb, 1994; AALM 79782
  - Notre Dame Today: Winter [Recordable Laserdisc], no date; AALM 79783
  - Notre Dame Library 1 [Recordable Laserdisc], no date; AALM 79784
- Alumni Association: Graphics, 1990s-; GALM
  - Digital Images, c2003-; GALM
    - Northwest Voyageurs - Two people mountain biking [stock photo], c2003; GALM
    - Northwest Voyageurs - Salmon Canyon [stock photo], c2003; GALM
    - Northwest Voyageurs - Two children in a raft on a river or lake [stock photo], c2003; GALM
    - Northwest Voyageurs - A man in a boat holding up a fish [stock photo], c2003; GALM
    - Northwest Voyageurs - [stock photo], c2003; GALM
    - Alumni Association Travel Tours brochure, 2003; GALM
    - Eck Visitors Center exteriors; photos by Bruce Harlan [38 photos], 2003/0517; GALM
    - Alumni Association Legacy Reception [21 jpg files; 20 .411 files], 2003; GALM
    - Monogram Club Alumni Newsletter - A man holding two Notre Dame door knockers, 2003; GALM
    - Monogram Club Alumni Newsletter - Portrait of a man wearing a Notre Dame baseball hat, 2003; GALM
    - Monogram Club Alumni Newsletter - Notre Dame door knockers [10 photos], 2003; GALM
    - Painting portrait of Rev. Edmund P. Joyce by McClancy; photos by Matt Cashore [26 photos], 2003/1205; GALM
    - Dedication of the Kansas Turnpike Authority Knute Rockne Memorial display at the Matfield Green Service Area, including Easter Heathman, Rockne family members, Rockne Memorial crash site marker; photos by Tim Brady [71 photos], 2004/0331; GALM
    - Alumni Association new Board of Directors members individual portraits; photos by Heather Gollatz-Dukeman [30 photos, scanned from negatives], 2004/0421; GALM
    - Alumni Association Young Alumni Luncheon in the Morris Inn - Young Alumni Award to Michael (Mike) Tribe, including Carol Mullaney, Jean Collier; photos by Heather Gollatz-Dukeman [29 photos, scanned from negatives], 2004/0422; GALM
    - Alumni Association Dinner in South Dining Hall, including Chuck Lennon, Jean Collier, Bob Sullivan, Chuck Lennon; photos by Heather Gollatz-Dukeman [15 photos, scanned from negatives], 2004/0423; GALM
    - Alumni Association Hall Spirit Awards and Distinguished Student Awards, including Chuck Lennon, Jean Collier, Carol Mullaney, Rev. Mark Poorman, Heather Rakoczy Russell, Kathleen Fox, William Conley, Rev. Paul Doyle; photos by Heather Gollatz-Dukeman [70 photos, scanned from negatives], 2004/0424; GALM
    - Alumni Association Rev. John J. Cavanaugh Award to Adam A. Milani and William D. Reynolds Award to Dr. Joseph A. DiCara lunch at Greenfields Cafe in the Hesburgh Center for International Studies, including Jean Collier; photos by Heather Gollatz-Dukeman [16 photos, scanned from negatives], 2004/0424; GALM
    - Football Pre-Game - Notre Dame vs. Michigan, including with Joe Kernan, Dave Duerson, Bob Sullivan, Chuck Lennon, Football Coach Tyrone Willingham, Jeanne Sullivan, Danielle Green, Army Golden Knights parachute team, Flag-Raising Ceremony, Irish Guard, ROTC Color Guard, Alumni Association Harvey G. Foster Award Presentation to Stephen L. Pavela Jr.; photos by Michael (Mike) Bennett [36 photos], 2004/0911; GALM
    - Football Pre-Game - Notre Dame vs. Michigan, including with Joe Kernan, Dave Duerson, Chuck Lennon, Football Coach Tyrone Willingham, Jeanne Sullivan, Bob Sullivan, Danielle Green, Army Golden Knights parachute team, Flag-Raising Ceremony, Irish Guard, ROTC Color Guard; photos by Heather Gollatz-Dukeman [36 photos, scanned from negatives], 2004/0911; GALM
    - Alumni Association Past Presidents group; photos by Heather Gollatz-Dukeman [3 photos, scanned from negatives], 2004/0910; GALM
    - Football Game Day - Notre Dame vs. Michigan - Alumni Association Harvey G. Foster Award Presentation to Stephen L. Pavela Jr., including with Chuck Lennon, Bob Sullivan; photos by Heather Gollatz-Dukeman [16 photos, scanned from negatives], 2004/0911; GALM
    - Football Game Day - Notre Dame vs. Michigan - Band Directors Ken Dye and Sam Sanchez on the sidelines; photo by Heather Gollatz-Dukeman [photo scanned from a negative], 2004/0911; GALM
    - Alumni Association Board of Directors group; photos by Heather Gollatz-Dukeman [4 photos, scanned from negatives], 2004/09; GALM
    - Alumni Association Board of Directors individual portraits; photos by Heather Gollatz-Dukeman [69 photos, scanned from negatives], 2004/09; GALM
    - Financial Executives Alumni Conference (FEAC) at the Mendoza College of Business, including inside Jordan Auditorium; photos by Matt Cashore [56 photos], 2004/0923; GALM
    - Mendoza College of Business exteriors; photos by Matt Cashore [5 photos], 2004/0923; GALM
    - Alumni Association Rev. William Corby Award to Ambassador Francis X. Taylor, including Constance Taylor, Chuck Lennon, Rev. Peter Rocca, Nancy Hanson, Anthony Hyder, Judy Petty, LTC Jordan Kelly; photos by Heather Gollatz-Dukeman [59 photos, scanned from negatives], 2004/1001; GALM
    - Football Game Day - Notre Dame vs. Purdue - Alumni Association Rev. William Corby Award Presentation to Ambassador Francis X. Taylor, including Constance Taylor, Chuck Lennon, Rev. Peter Rocca; photos by Heather Gollatz-Dukeman [10 photos], 2004/1002; GALM
    - Football Game Day - Notre Dame vs. Pittsburgh - Alumni Association Family Exemplar Award Presentation to Karen Phelps and Jamie Moyer, including with Chuck Lennon, Jean Collier, their children, the Irish Guard; photos by Heather Gollatz-Dukeman [8 photos], 2004/1113; GALM
    - Alumni Association Family Exemplar Award to Karen Phelps Moyer and Jamie Moyer Dinner, including with Chuck Lennon, Lou Nanni, Digger Phelps, Jean Collier; photos by Heather Gollatz-Dukeman [58 photos], 2004/1112; GALM
    - Football Game Pep Rally - Notre Dame vs. Pittsburgh, including Alumni Association Director Chuck Lennon, Football Coach Tyrone Willingham; photos by Heather Gollatz-Dukeman [6 photos], 2004/1112; GALM
    - Alumni Senate Leadership Conference, including Mike Brown, Karen Putt [17 photos; camera time stamp is probably inaccurate], 2004/04; GALM
    - Alumni Senate Leadership Conference Undergraduate Admission and Office of Student Financial Services PowerPoint presentation [GALM-2004-0423-Saracino_Russo_Alumni_Senate204.ppt], GALM